Blueprint UP268
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Blueprint
2014
2011 -- 2017
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
University Advancement Division
UP268
0.5 Linear Feet
5 Digital Object(s)
96 Megabytes
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains Blueprint a publication put out by the University Advancement. Blueprint is published three times a year for alumni, parents, and friends who generously support Tufts University as donors and volunteers.
- Blueprint, 2011 -- 2017; UP268.001; 5 Digital Object(s); 96 Megabytes; 0.5 Linear Feet
  - Blueprint, Spring 2011; UP268.001.001.00006 (Volume 1)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Open for research.
    Scope and Contents
    News of giving, growth, and gratitude.
    magazine (periodical)
  - Blueprint, Winter 2014; UP268.001.001.00005 (Volume 1)
  - Blueprint, Spring 2014; UP268.001.001.00001 (Volume 1)
  - Blueprint, Fall 2014; UP268.001.001.00002 (Volume 1)
  - Blueprint, Winter 2015; UP268.001.001.00003 (Volume 1)
  - Blueprint, Spring 2015; UP268.001.001.00004 (Volume 1)
  - Blueprint, Winter 2016; UP268.001.00001; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Blueprint, Spring 2016; UP268.001.001.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Volume 1, Folder 7)
  - Blueprint, Fall 2016; UP268.001.00002; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Blueprint, Winter 2017; UP268.001.001.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Volume 1)
  - Blueprint, Spring 2017; UP268.001.00003; 1 Digital Object(s)